DAISY HUNT

UI Designer



+44 7719 628 156



hello@daisyhunt.com



London, UK



daisyhunt.com

UI Designer with a background in administration and hospitality. Experience working and communicating with different stakeholders and understanding customer motivations and frustrations. Pursuing a career change to challenge creative passions and to design products that positively impact how people interact with the world around them.

EDUCATION

2020-2021

User Interface Design & Frontend Development

Career Foundry

580+ hours of study and practical projects

2014-2015

PG Cert International Business Mountbatten Institute, New York

2009 - 2013

Event Management BSc Sheffield Hallam University 1st Class Honors

PROJECTS

2021

Portfolio website UI Design | Frontend Development

Portfolio website - daisyhunt.com - built to showcase my work. Built whilst learning HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

2020

WhereTo Responsive Web App UX Design | UI Design

Solo project focussed on user research, wireframes, user testing and responsive designs. View at daisyhunt.com

2020

ShareOut Native App UI Design

Solo project focussed on concept, wireframes, native design guidelines, iconography and prototyping. View at daisyhunt.com

SKILLS

UX Design

User Research User Personas Task Flows

UI Design

Wireframes
Prototyping
Iconography
Interaction Design
Style Guides
User Testing

FrontendDevelopment

HTML CSS JavaScript

Tools

Adobe XD InVision Usability Hub Atom GitHub Microsoft Office

WORK EXPERIENCE

• 2015-Present

Sales Support Administrator

Euromoney Institutional Investor | London, UK

- Unique role as central sales support across 8 financial publications.
- Responsible for processing sales, credit control, customer service and data management.
- Central point of contact for clients, sales, finance and marketing.
- 0 2014-2015

Administrator

2x4 | New York, USA

- PA, front desk receptionist and office manager at a successful global design firm.
- Gained an understanding of the design industry including strategy and branding.
- Handled all incoming enquiries and provided office support to all areas of the business.
- 0 2012-2014

Event Administrative Assistant

Searcy's @ The Pump Room | Bath, UK

- Responsible for all administration and liaison with event, restaurant, marketing and finance .
- Designed promotional material for events.
- Compiled and managed databases of client and event information.
- 2008 2014

Various hospitality roles

- Roles as waitress, event hostess, cocktail mixologist and barista.
- Regularly required to problem solve and handle customer queries and requests.